site44.com 2019-06-16

# site44 -Privacy Policy

Planet Rational, Inc. (" ** _We_** " or " ** _Planet Rational_** ") owns and operates the website www.Site44.com through which it offers services and software that permit anyone to create, host and publish web content (the website, services and software are collectively referred to as the " ** _Service_** " throughout this Privacy Policy). 

The privacy of our visitors and customers is very important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how we use the information that you provide to us when using our services or when visiting our website. 

This Privacy Policy incorporates these principles. 

Note, we’ve decided to make the below Privacy Policy available under a Creative Commons Sharealike license, which means you’re more than welcome to steal it and repurpose it for your own use, just make sure to replace references to us with ones to you. We adapted the Privacy Policy from WordPress.com in generating our Privacy Policy, and we greatly appreciate their generosity in sharing it. 

* ## Information We Collect 

Certain visitors to Planet Rational’s websites may choose to interact with Planet Rational in ways that require Planet Rational to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Planet Rational may gather will depend on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a website through our Service to provide their name and email address. Those who engage in financial transactions with Planet Rational may be asked to provide additional information, including address, phone number, and debit card or credit card information. In each case, Planet Rational collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Planet Rational. Planet Rational does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

* ## How We Collect Information 

We may ask you for personal information, including your name, postal address, phone number, email address, and social website account names, when you register, subscribe, create an account, purchase services from us, or otherwise interact with the Service or contact Planet Rational. We may also track the websites you view and the comments you make to the forums, bulletin boards, discussion groups, chat rooms or other methods of communication that may be offered on or through our Service from time to time, or to those related to our social media pages or accounts. We use cookies and related technologies to collect information about your computer and your interaction with the Service and our business partner websites. You can read more about cookies and other technologies in the Cookies and Related Technologies section. 

* ## Information We Disclose 

Planet Rational discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Planet Rational’s behalf or to provide services available at Planet Rational’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Planet Rational’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. We will protect the privacy and security of personally-identifying Information according to our Privacy Policy, regardless of where it is processed or stored. 

Planet Rational will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Planet Rational discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Planet Rational believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Planet Rational, third parties or the public at large. 

If you are a registered user of an Planet Rational website and have supplied your email address, Planet Rational may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Planet Rational and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. 

If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Planet Rational maintains reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

* ## Cookies and Related Technologies 

Planet Rational may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to our website or to websites created using our Service by using cookies and other technologies. 

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Planet Rational uses cookies to help Planet Rational identify and track visitors, their usage of Planet Rational websites, and their website access preferences. Some cookies contain serial numbers that allow us to connect your activity with other information we store about you in your profile (if you are a registered user) or as related to your interactions with our Service. Planet Rational visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Planet Rational’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Planet Rational’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

We may collect many different types of information from cookies and other technologies, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Planet Rational’s purpose in collecting non-personally-identifying information is to better understand how Planet Rational’s visitors use its websites. From time to time, Planet Rational may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its websites. 

Planet Rational also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. An IP address is a unique identifier that devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. Planet Rational only discloses logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Planet Rational may also use pixel tags, clear gifs and web beacons to help us better understand how you use our Service and to customize your experience with our Service. Pixel tags, clear gifs, and web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on website pages or in our emails that allow us to determine whether you have performed specific actions. When you access these pages or open email messages, the pixel tags and web beacons generate a notice of that action to us, or our service providers. These tools allow us to measure response to our communications and improve our web pages and promotions. 

* ## Business Transfers 

If Planet Rational, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Planet Rational goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Planet Rational may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

* ## Advertising 

Planet Rational may maintain relationships with third party advertising companies to place advertisements on our behalf onto other websites or the websites created using our Service, and to perform tracking and reporting functions for these customer websites and our advertisements. We do not share personally-identifying information with third party advertising companies; however, these third parties may automatically collect information about your visit to our websites and other websites, your IP address, your internet service provider, and the browser you use when you visit our websites. They do this by using cookies, clear gifs and other technologies (refer to the information provided in this Privacy Policy about cookies and related technologies). Information collected may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of our websites and the other websites tracked by these third parties. 

This Privacy Policy does not cover the collection methods or use of the information collected by these third parties, and Planet Rational is not responsible for cookies or clear gifs in third party ads. We encourage you to review the privacy policies or statements of these third party advertising companies to learn more about their use of cookies and other technologies. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by third party advertisers, please visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

* ## Correcting Personal Information 

You can access, update and delete your contact information, financial account information, and the other information you provided to use in your profile by logging into your account on the Service or by sending us an email at [privacy@site44.com](mailto:privacy@site44.com). 

If you want to close your account or have other questions or requests, please contact us using the information provided in this Privacy Policy. Please note that while we are ready to assist you in managing your subscriptions, closing your account, and removing your active profile, we cannot always delete records of past interactions and transactions. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services and to maintain a record of your transactions for financial reporting purposes. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us using the information provided below. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

* ## Privacy Policy Changes 

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy to clarify our practices or to reflect new or different privacy practices, such as when we add new features to our Service. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account, if any) or by means of notice on the Service prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information about our privacy practices. 

* ## Questions 

If you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy, you may address them to Planet Rational, Inc., 15600 N.E. 8th Street, Suite B1-717, Bellevue, WA 98008, or by email at [privacy@site44.com](mailto:privacy@site44.com).
